[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Asia"], "TIME": ["day this morning"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "What the hell is going on, Ali?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "hell", "is", "going", "on", ",", "Ali", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "Look, we started off the day this morning with a rough night in Asia.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "we", "started", "off", "the", "day", "this", "morning", "with", "a", "rough", "night", "in", "Asia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Is this looking more likely now, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "looking", "more", "likely", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Is this then a crisis caused by politics rather than straightforward economics?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "then", "a", "crisis", "caused", "by", "politics", "rather", "than", "straightforward", "economics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "It absolutely is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "absolutely", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "When do you sleep?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "you", "sleep", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "After this.", "answer_tokens": ["After", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What should people be doing right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "people", "be", "doing", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, you shouldn't be afraid if you are sticking around for the long-term.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "should", "n't", "be", "afraid", "if", "you", "are", "sticking", "around", "for", "the", "long-term", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "If the Feds run out of bullets, what does the president have in his locker that he can do that is dramatic enough to stop this market mayhem?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "Feds", "run", "out", "of", "bullets", ",", "what", "does", "the", "president", "have", "in", "his", "locker", "that", "he", "can", "do", "that", "is", "dramatic", "enough", "to", "stop", "this", "market", "mayhem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, I think the most obvious thing he can do is something about jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "most", "obvious", "thing", "he", "can", "do", "is", "something", "about", "jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "But, Leigh, wouldn't that mean that the president actually would have to -- it would have to be another stimulus, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "Leigh", ",", "would", "n't", "that", "mean", "that", "the", "president", "actually", "would", "have", "to", "--", "it", "would", "have", "to", "be", "another", "stimulus", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "There would have to be spending.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "would", "have", "to", "be", "spending", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leigh"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Neel, first to you?", "question_tokens": ["Neel", ",", "first", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I think that we need to focus on spending.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "need", "to", "focus", "on", "spending", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Neel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Neel"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Ali, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Ali", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Unfortunately, Neel's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Unfortunately", ",", "Neel", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "And is it something that is conducted at the center?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "something", "that", "is", "conducted", "at", "the", "center", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, I'm running for the presidency of the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "running", "for", "the", "presidency", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "being", "so", "weird", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "I'm not being weird about this, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "being", "weird", "about", "this", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", "as", "a", "host", ",", "if", "I", "say", "this", "is", "what", "I", "want", "to", "talk", "about", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "we", "should", "address", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Not really, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["6:00"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "You're leaving?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "leaving", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, I was supposed to be speaking at the Republican women's club at 6:00, and I chose to be a little late for that, not to be -- you know, yes, not to endure rude talk show hosts, but to talk to you about my book and to talk about the issues that I address in my book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "supposed", "to", "be", "speaking", "at", "the", "Republican", "women", "'s", "club", "at", "6:00", ",", "and", "I", "chose", "to", "be", "a", "little", "late", "for", "that", ",", "not", "to", "be", "--", "you", "know", ",", "yes", ",", "not", "to", "endure", "rude", "talk", "show", "hosts", ",", "but", "to", "talk", "to", "you", "about", "my", "book", "and", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "issues", "that", "I", "address", "in", "my", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Have you read the book?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "read", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Yes, but these issues are in your book.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "these", "issues", "are", "in", "your", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Are we done?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "He's still there.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "still", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Or was I behaving in a perfectly irresponsible journalistic manner?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "I", "behaving", "in", "a", "perfectly", "irresponsible", "journalistic", "manner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I thought your questions are perfectly fine.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "your", "questions", "are", "perfectly", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Todd, what did you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["Todd", ",", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, I thought -- I thought it was fascinating that she managed to push back on you when you were asking these questions without making any effort to really try to dodge them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "--", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "fascinating", "that", "she", "managed", "to", "push", "back", "on", "you", "when", "you", "were", "asking", "these", "questions", "without", "making", "any", "effort", "to", "really", "try", "to", "dodge", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "And is it something that is conducted at that center?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "something", "that", "is", "conducted", "at", "that", "center", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, I'm running for the presidency of the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "running", "for", "the", "presidency", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Todd, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Todd", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Yes, I think that's absolutely true.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "absolutely", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Is there any doubt in your mind that you will be able to function in such circumstances?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "doubt", "in", "your", "mind", "that", "you", "will", "be", "able", "to", "function", "in", "such", "circumstances", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "A rock 'n' roll wild man, huh?", "question_tokens": ["A", "rock", "'n", "'", "roll", "wild", "man", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "''", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "We've had a bit of battles this week, as you may be aware.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "had", "a", "bit", "of", "battles", "this", "week", ",", "as", "you", "may", "be", "aware", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Have you ever walked out of an interview?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "walked", "out", "of", "an", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Could you imagine doing that?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "No, I would argue -- I mean, I would argue with you.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "would", "argue", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "would", "argue", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What do you make of what is happening to your country's economy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "is", "happening", "to", "your", "country", "'s", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I think I answered that question with the title of the album.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "answered", "that", "question", "with", "the", "title", "of", "the", "album", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Is it the politicians?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "politicians", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "It's all of the above.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "of", "the", "above", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "I think -- I think.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "And I was working.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "was", "working", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Are you OK?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Yeah, I'm fine.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "'m", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Time to slow down a little bit?", "question_tokens": ["Time", "to", "slow", "down", "a", "little", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Yeah, probably have to slow down a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "probably", "have", "to", "slow", "down", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Around 43 million.", "answer_tokens": ["Around", "43", "million", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Dare I ask how much money it has made you?", "question_tokens": ["Dare", "I", "ask", "how", "much", "money", "it", "has", "made", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "It hasn't made hardly any money for me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "has", "n't", "made", "hardly", "any", "money", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1982"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "They declared me in breach of contract in 1982.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "declared", "me", "in", "breach", "of", "contract", "in", "1982", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "So you sell 43 million copies of this album and barely made any money out of it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "sell", "43", "million", "copies", "of", "this", "album", "and", "barely", "made", "any", "money", "out", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I think I got a check last week for 1.29.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "got", "a", "check", "last", "week", "for", "1.29", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "In total, have you made less than say a million dollars out of that?", "question_tokens": ["In", "total", ",", "have", "you", "made", "less", "than", "say", "a", "million", "dollars", "out", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "No, I've made more because we -- we did take them to court at one point.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "made", "more", "because", "we", "--", "we", "did", "take", "them", "to", "court", "at", "one", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["million dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", ":", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "When that -- and \"The Paradise,\" I was around 300, 310.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "that", "--", "and", "``", "The", "Paradise", ",", "''", "I", "was", "around", "300", ",", "310", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "What are you now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, I've gained seven pounds, so I'm sorry you asked me that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "gained", "seven", "pounds", ",", "so", "I", "'m", "sorry", "you", "asked", "me", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "CC", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "What's your fighting weight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "fighting", "weight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "A hundred and twenty, no.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "hundred", "and", "twenty", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Do you know who you're going to vote for next election?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "who", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "vote", "for", "next", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "EAT LOAF: I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["EAT", "LOAF", ":", "I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "How did you end up at Meat Loaf?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "end", "up", "at", "Meat", "Loaf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "You were still called Marvin at the time?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "still", "called", "Marvin", "at", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "No, I was called Meat.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "called", "Meat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marvin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Are you now legally called Meat Loaf?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "now", "legally", "called", "Meat", "Loaf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I had Meat Loaf on my passport when we first were touring \"Bat Out of Hell.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "Meat", "Loaf", "on", "my", "passport", "when", "we", "first", "were", "touring", "``", "Bat", "Out", "of", "Hell", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Lee Aday"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "What is on your passport?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "on", "your", "passport", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Michael Lee Aday.", "answer_tokens": ["Michael", "Lee", "Aday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1984"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "So that's your -- you go by that name legally?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "'s", "your", "--", "you", "go", "by", "that", "name", "legally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Yes, since 1984.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "since", "1984", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Do you like to be called Mr. Loaf?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "to", "be", "called", "Mr.", "Loaf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Meat.", "answer_tokens": ["Meat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Loaf"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Meat?", "question_tokens": ["Meat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "You were struck on the head with a shot during a shot put event?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "struck", "on", "the", "head", "with", "a", "shot", "during", "a", "shot", "put", "event", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "It was at practice, but it was 62 feet with a 12- pound shot.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "at", "practice", ",", "but", "it", "was", "62", "feet", "with", "a", "12-", "pound", "shot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Wolf Parkinson White"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "A compliment?", "question_tokens": ["A", "compliment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Yes, Wolf Parkinson White.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Wolf", "Parkinson", "White", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Are you very unlucky or are you very lucky, because you're still alive?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "very", "unlucky", "or", "are", "you", "very", "lucky", ",", "because", "you", "'re", "still", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "I'm very lucky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "lucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine O'Donnell"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "If you could vote for anyone right now, who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "vote", "for", "anyone", "right", "now", ",", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Christine O'Donnell.", "answer_tokens": ["Christine", "O'Donnell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Who's that?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Chris Christie, governor of New Jersey.", "answer_tokens": ["Chris", "Christie", ",", "governor", "of", "New", "Jersey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "being", "so", "weird", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I'm not being weird.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "being", "weird", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "And if you're going, go.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "'re", "going", ",", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Are we off?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Larry, you're being inappropriate.", "answer_tokens": ["Larry", ",", "you", "'re", "being", "inappropriate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 696, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "I'm not going to talk about --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "talk", "about", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "What's your question?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "It's the weirdest interview you'll ever see.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "weirdest", "interview", "you", "'ll", "ever", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gene Simmons", "Joy Behar"]}, "docId": "110818pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "What sent Fergie complete economy off the rails?", "question_tokens": ["What", "sent", "Fergie", "complete", "economy", "off", "the", "rails", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Kiss front man Gene Simmons was being interviewed with his significant other of 28 years when Joy Behar brought up his claim that he slept with 5,000 women.", "answer_tokens": ["Kiss", "front", "man", "Gene", "Simmons", "was", "being", "interviewed", "with", "his", "significant", "other", "of", "28", "years", "when", "Joy", "Behar", "brought", "up", "his", "claim", "that", "he", "slept", "with", "5,000", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fergie"]}}]